How is my heart to forget you?
كيف لقلبي أن ينساك
O one who is longing to see you
يا من أحن إلى رؤياك
In my intensity of my hope, I will remain, O Lord, I love you
في شدتي من أملي سواك سأظل يا ربي أهواك
Who is always with me?
يا من بحالي دوما عليم
وقفت ببابك أنت الكريم
I stood by your door
Lord, you are my hope, accept my plea and forgive my sins, O merciful
ربي أنت رجائي فإقبل دعائي واعفو عن ذنبي يا رحيم
الله
You created me at best
خلقتني في أحسن حال
you gift me without question
ورزقتني من دون سؤال
In a prostration in the darkness of the night, I mentioned my Lord my tears fill down
في سجدة في جوف الليل ذكرت ربي دمعي سال
Who is always with me?
يا من بحالي دوما عليم
I stood by your door
وقفت ببابك أنت الكريم
ربي أنت رجائي فإقبل دعائي واعفو عن ذنبي يا رحيم
الله
يا من بحالي دوما عليم    وقفت ببابك أنت الكريم ربي أنت رجائي فإقبل دعائي واعفو عن ذنبي يا رحيم
Allah
ربي أنت رجائي فإقبل  دعائي واعفو عن ذنبي يا رحيم